A Guide to the Cocke Family Papers 1800-1871
Special Collections Department, University of Virginia Library
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
Cocke Family Papers 1800-1871
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
5213-b
This collection consists of 528 items.
Administrative Information
Access
There are no restrictions.
Scope and Content Information
This collection consists of letters, chiefly containing family news. There is also a bill from Fisher and Bird, Norfolk, to Alexander Jackson Davis regarding the price of marble and granite; memorabilia from an 1855 tour of Europe; a bookplate of Gouverneur Morris; a photograph of the barn at "Bremo," the family estate; genealogical material; and the diaries, 1820-1842, of Louisa Maxwell Holmes Cocke.
Correspondents include William Daniel Cabell, Ann Blaws Barraud, John Hartwell Cocke, Ann Carter Oliver, Nannie Oliver, Lucy Oliver, Merit M. Robinson, Philip Barraud, and members of the Braxton family.
Arrangement
This collection is arranged chronologically.
Additional Descriptive Data
Separated Material
Removed and filed in MSS 640:
Diary of Mrs. Louisa Cocke, 1820 January 2-August 9
Diary of Mrs. Louisa Cocke, 1821 December 4- 1823 December 20
Diary of Mrs. Louisa Cocke, 1825 October 18- 1826 July 4 (copy)
Diary of Mrs. Louisa Cocke, 1826 July 5- 1827 September (copy)
Contents List
- Mrs. M. K. Banks to Miss Louisa Maxwell 1800 January 28 (Box 1)
- Rebecca Calvert to Miss Louisa Maxwell 1803 September 10 (Box 1)
- Martha King to Miss Louisa Maxwell 1803 September 17 (Box 1)
- Martha King to Miss Louisa Maxwell 1803 October 8 (Box 1)
- Rebecca Calvert to Miss Louisa Maxwell 1804 August 4 (Box 1)
- J. H. Read, Jr. to Dr. Robert Holmes 1804 September 20 (Box 1)
- Mrs. L. Read to Miss Louisa Maxwell 1805 February 24 (Box 1)
- Mrs. Mary Cowan to Miss Louisa Maxwell 1805 July 20 (Box 1)
- Mrs. Mary Cowan to Miss Louisa Maxwell 1805 October 6 (Box 1)
- Lucy F. Smith to Miss Louisa Maxwell 1805 October 9 (Box 1)
- William Maxwell to Mrs. Louisa Holmes 1808 October 6 (Box 1)
- Wm. Pettit to John H. Cocke 1809 April 25 (Box 1)
- Samuel Holmes to Mrs. Louisa Holmes 1815 February 19 (Box 1)
- Mr. Samuel Holmes to Mrs. Louisa Holmes 1816 August 6 (Box 1)
- M. Sawyer to Mrs. Louisa Holmes 1816 (Box 1)
- Mrs. S. Flintham to Mrs. Louisa Holmes 1817 August 15 (Box 1)
- Lucy F. Smith to Mrs. Louisa Holmes 1817 September 24 (Box 1)
- T. L. Mitchell to Mrs. Louisa Holmes 1817 November 20 (Box 1)
- Samuel Holmes to Mrs. Louisa Holmes 1817 November 25 (Box 1)
- I. Nicholson Campbell to Mrs. Louisa Holmes 1818 April 10 (Box 1)
- Mrs. Lucy F. Smith to Mrs. Louisa Holmes 1818 August 12 (Box 1)
- Mrs. S. Flintham to Mrs. Louisa Holmes 1818 October 6 (Box 1)
- Mrs. Lucy F. Smith to Mrs. Louisa Holmes 1818 October 21 (Box 1)
- E. Cowan to Mrs. Louisa Holmes 1819 April 8 (Box 1)
- Mrs. S. Flintham to Mrs. Louisa Holmes 1819 May 3 (Box 1)
- William Maxwell to Mrs. Louisa Holmes 1819 May 22 (Box 1)
- Mrs. S. Flintham to Mrs. Louisa Holmes 1819 June 4 (Box 1)
- Mrs. S. Flintham to Mrs. Louisa Holmes 1819 September 17 (Box 1)
- Mrs. Lucy F. Smith to Mrs. Louisa Holmes 1819 October 3 (Box 1)
- Mrs. S. Flintham to Mrs. Louisa Holmes 1819 November 22 (Box 1)
- Mrs. S. B. Purcell to Mrs. Louisa Holmes 1820 January 20 (Box 1)
- Mrs. S. Flintham to Mrs. Louisa Holmes 1820 March 1 (Box 1)
- Thomas M. Strong to Mrs. Louisa Holmes 1820 April 5 (Box 1)
- Mrs. Mary Cowan to Mrs. Louisa Holmes 1820 May 1 (Box 1)
- Mrs. S. B. Purcell to Mrs. Louisa Holmes 1820 May 22 (Box 1)
- Diary of Louisa Cocke 1820 August 9- 1821 March 8 (Box 1)
- Lucy F. Smith to Mrs. Louisa Holmes 1820 September 22 (Box 1)
- Diary of Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1821 April 1- December 4 (Box 1)
- I. D. Paxton to Mrs. Louisa Holmes 1821 May 7 (Box 1)
- General John H. Cocke to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1821 May 28 (Box 1)
- General John H. Cocke to Mrs. Louisa Holmes 1821 May 29 (Box 1)
- General John H. Cocke to Mrs. Louisa Holmes 1821 May 30 (Box 1)
- General John H. Cocke to Mrs. Louisa Holmes 1821 June 5 (Box 1)
- General John H. Cocketo Mrs. Louisa Holmes 1821 June 10 (Box 1)
- General John H. Cocke to Mrs. Louisa Holmes 1821 June 17 (Box 1)
- General John H. Cocke to Mrs. Louisa Holmes 1821 June 25 (Box 1)
- General John H. Cocke to Mrs. Louisa Holmes 1821 July 3 (Box 1)
- General John H. Cocke to Mrs. Louisa Holmes 1821 July 9 (Box 1)
- General John H. Cocke to Mrs. Louisa Holmes 1821 July 10 (Box 1)
- Mrs. Virginia Cary to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1822 August 30 (Box 1)
- Sketch to Bremo Gardens 1822 (Box 1)
- General John H. Cocke to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1823 January 16 (Box 2)
- Mrs. Sally Faulcon to Mrs. [Louisa] Cocke 1823 February 4 (Box 1)
- Misses Mary Malvina Terrell to [Mrs. Louisa Cocke] 1823 April 2 (Box 2)
- Joseph C. Cabell to [Mrs. Louisa Cocke] 1823 April 8 (Box 1)
- Mrs. R. Harrison to [Mrs. Louisa Cocke] 1823 April 18 (Box 2)
- Mrs. L. [B.] Faulcon to [Mrs. Louisa Cocke] 1823 April 22 (Box 2)
- Miss Mary E. Terrell to [Mrs. Louisa Cocke] [1823] April (Box 2)
- Mrs. Virginia Cary to Mrs. [Louisa] Cocke 1823 May 13 (Box 2)
- General John H. Cocke to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1823 June 4 (Box 2)
- General John H. Cocke to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1823 June 10 (Box 2)
- General John H. Cocke to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1823 June 14 (Box 2)
- P[hilip]; S[t.]; G[eorge] Cocke to [Mrs. Louisa Cocke] 1823 June 21 (Box 1)
- General John H. Cocke to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1823 June 23 (Box 2)
- [Mrs.] Luch F. Smith to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1823 August 28 (Box 2)
- General John H. Cocke to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1823 December 10 (Box 2)
- General John H. Cocke to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1823 December 17 (Box 2)
- Mrs. Louisa Cocke to Cary C. Cocke 1823 (Box 2)
- General John H. Cocke to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1824 May 13 (Box 2)
- General John H. Cocke to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1824 May 13 (Box 2)
- General John H. & Miss Louisiana Cocke to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1824 May 18 (Box 2)
- General John H. Cocke to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1824 May 27 (Box 2)
- General John H. Cocke to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1824 October 3 (Box 2)
- General John H. Cocke to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1824 November 15 (Box 2)
- General John H. Cocke to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1824 December 7 (Box 2)
- General John H. Cocke to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1824 December 9 (Box 2)
- General John H. Cocke to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1824 December 16 (Box 2)
- Ann B. Cocke to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1825 January 8 (Box 1)
- Mrs. Nicholas Faulcon, Jr. to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1825 January 10 (Box 2)
- General John H. Cocke to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1825 February 3 (Box 2)
- Mrs. Sarah Wilson to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1825 February 4 (Box 2)
- Mrs. James Maxwell to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1825 February 8 (Box 2)
- Louisiana B. Cocke to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1825 February 22 (Box 2)
- Mrs. I. H. Rice to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1825 March 4 (Box 2)
- Malvina T. Terrell to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1825 March 7 (Box 2)
- Susan Maxwell to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1825 March 15 (Box 2)
- Francis Bowman to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1825 April 6 (Box 1)
- Miss Mary E. Terrell to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1825 April 6 (Box 2)
- Malvina Terrell to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1825 April 8 (Box 2)
- Louisiana B. Cocke to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1825 April 12 (Box 2)
- Malvina Terrell to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1825 April 12 (Box 2)
- Mrs. Sally Faulcon to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1825 April 13 (Box 2)
- Mrs. James Maxwell to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1825 April 26 (Box 2)
- Mrs. Anne R. Rice to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1825 April 30 (Box 2)
- Miss Augusta Ellen Granbery to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1825 May 3 (Box 2)
- Louisiana B. Cocke to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1825 May 3 (Box 2)
- Mrs. Sally Faulcon to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1825 June 8 (Box 2)
- Miss Mary E. Terrell to Louisa Cocke 1825 July 23 (Box 2)
- Mrs. Sarah Wilson to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1825 July 27 (Box 2)
- Mrs. Virginia Cary to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1825 August 13 (Box 2)
- Mrs. H. M. Stribling to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1825 August 16 (Box 2)
- Mrs. Virginia Cary to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1825 August 17 (Box 2)
- Mrs. James Maxwell to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1825 August 25 (Box 2)
- Mrs. Margaret R. Cabell to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1825 September 2 (Box 2)
- Mrs. Virginia Cary to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1825 September 13 (Box 2)
- Miss Mary E. Terrell to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1825 September 21 (Box 2)
- Mrs. Sally Faulcon to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1825 October 1 (Box 2)
- Mr. Cary C. Cocke to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1825 October 2 (Box 2)
- Ann B. Cocke to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1825 October 8 (Box 2)
- Ann B. Cocke to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1825 October 29 (Box 2)
- Mrs. Sally Faulcon to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1825 November 1 (Box 2)
- Mrs. Virginia Cary to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1825 November 6 (Box 2)
- Ann B. Cocke to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1825 November 13 (Box 2)
- Mrs. Virginia Cary to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1825 November 24 (Box 2)
- Cary C. Cocke to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1825 November 29 (Box 2)
- Ann B. Cocke to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1825 December 26 (Box 2)
- Cary C. Cocke to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1825 January (Box 1)
- Mrs. Virginia Cary to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1825 December (Box 2)
- General John H. Cocke to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1826 January 4 (Box 2)
- General John H. Cocke to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1826 January 17 (Box 2)
- General John H. Cocke to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1826 January 18 (Box 2)
- Mrs. Louisa Cocke to Cary C. Cocke 1826 February 9 (Box 2)
- Mrs. Sally Faulcon to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1826 February 14 (Box 2)
- Miss Mary E. Terrell to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1826 February 15 (Box 2)
- Mrs. Sukey [J.] Harrison to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1826 February 18 (Box 2)
- Mrs. James Maxwell to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1826 February 28 (Box 2)
- Mrs. Virginia Cary to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1826 February (Box 2)
- General John H. Cocke to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1826 March 4 (Box 2)
- General John H. Cocke and Louisiana Faulcon to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1826 March 6 (Box 2)
- Mrs. Louisa Cocke to Cary C. Cocke 1826 March 9 (Box 2)
- Virginia Cary to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1826 March 9 (Box 2)
- Mrs. Sukey [J.] Harrison to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1826 March 11 (Box 2)
- Ann B. Cocke to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1826 March 13 (Box 2)
- Virginia Cary to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1826 March 14 (Box 2)
- Mrs. Randolph Harrison to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1826 March 18 (Box 2)
- Miss Lousiana B. Cocke to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1826 March 21 (Box 2)
- Miss Louisiana B. Cocke to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1826 March 27 (Box 2)
- Mrs. Sukey [J.] Harrison to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1826 March 27 (Box 2)
- Miss Ann B. Cocke to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1826 April 3 (Box 2)
- Miss M. E. Terrell to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1826 April 3, 4, & 15 (Box 2)
- Mrs. Elizabeth Moncure to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1826 April 6 (Box 2)
- Miss Louisiana B. Cocke to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1826 April 10 (Box 2)
- Mr. Randolph Harrison to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1826 April 11 (Box 2)
- Ann B. Cocke to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1826 April 16 (Box 2)
- M. T. Terrell to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1826 April 18 (Box 2)
- Louisiana B. Cocke to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1826 April 19 (Box 2)
- M. E. Tucker to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1826 April 19 (Box 2)
- Mrs. Sukey [J.] Harrison to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1826 April 21 (Box 2)
- General John H. Cocke to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1826 April 22 (Box 2)
- Louisiana B. Cocke to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1826 April 26 (Box 2)
- B. E. Payne to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1826 April 29 (Box 2)
- Mrs. Sally Faulcon to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1826 May 1 (Box 2)
- General John H. Cocke to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1826 May 2 (Box 2)
- Mrs. Randolph Harrison to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1826 May 5 (Box 2)
- General John H. Cocke to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1826 May 8 (Box 2)
- Louisiana B. Cocke to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1826 May 9 (Box 2)
- Mrs. James Maxwell to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1826 May 16 (Box 2)
- General John H. Cocke to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1826 May 17 (Box 2)
- Mrs. Jane Randolph to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1826 May 19 (Box 2)
- Sarah Wilson to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1826 May 22 (Box 2)
- Miss Mary E. Terrell to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1826 May 29 (Box 2)
- B. E. Payne to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1826 May 30 (Box 2)
- B. E. Payne to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1826 June 12 (Box 2)
- Miss Mary E. Terrell to Mrs. & Misses Cocke 1826 June 20 (Box 2)
- General John H. Cocke to Mrs. Louisiana Cocke 1826 June 23 (Box 2)
- Diary of Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1826 July 5- 1827 September 2 (Box 3)
- Mrs. Nicholas Faulcon to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1826 July 12 (Box 3)
- General John H. Cocke to Cary C. Cocke 1826 July 23 (Box 3)
- Miss Mary E. Terrell to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1826 August 1 (Box 3)
- Virginia Cary to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1826 August 30 (Box 3)
- Mrs. Augusta Randolph to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1826 August (Box 3)
- Miss Mary E. Terrell to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1826 September 22 (Box 3)
- General John H. Cocke to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1826 October 4 (Box 3)
- Mrs. H. C. Harrison to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1826 October 5 (Box 3)
- General John H. Cocke to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1826 October 24 (Box 3)
- General John H. Cocke to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1826 October 24 (Box 3)
- Dr. Henry W. Tucker to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1826 October 25 (Box 3)
- Mrs. James Maxwell to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1826 November 4 (Box 3)
- Mr. I. I. Royall to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1826 November 17 (Box 3)
- Mrs. Sukey [J.] Harrison to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1826 December 5 (Box 3)
- General John H. Cocke to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1826 December 8 (Box 3)
- General John H. Cocke to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1826 December 11 (Box 3)
- Mrs. Sally Faulcon to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1826 December 17 (Box 3)
- Sally F. Cocke to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1826 December 27 (Box 3)
- General John H. Cocke to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1827 February 28 (Box 3)
- General John H. Cocke to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1827 April 18 (Box 3)
- General John H. Cocke to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1827 April 22 (Box 3)
- Miss Susan I. Harrison to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1828 January 4 (Box 3)
- Mrs. John Faulcon to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1828 January 15 (Box 3)
- Mrs. Susan I. Harrison to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1828 January 16 (Box 3)
- General John H. Cocke to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1828 January 21 (Box 3)
- Mrs. S. A. Pool to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1828 January 25 (Box 3)
- Rev. S. Hurd to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1828 January 29 (Box 3)
- General John H. Cocke to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1828 January 30 (Box 3)
- Mrs. John Faulcon to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1828 February 13 (Box 3)
- Miss Malvina T. Terrell to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1828 March 2 (Box 3)
- Mrs. S. A. Pool to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1828 March 9 (Box 3)
- Mrs. John Faulcon to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1828 March 14 (Box 3)
- Mr. P. Suit to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1828 March 23 (Box 3)
- Rev. S. Hurd to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1828 April 3 (Box 3)
- Mrs. John Faulcon to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1828 April 23 (Box 3)
- General John H. Cocke to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1828 April 29 (Box 3)
- Mrs. John Faulcon to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1828 April 29 (Box 3)
- Miss Ann B. Cocke to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1828 April 29 (Box 3)
- Mrs. Sally Faulcon to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1828 May 5 (Box 3)
- Miss Mary E. Terrell to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1828 May 13 (Box 3)
- General John H. Cocke to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1828 May 15 (Box 3)
- Miss Sally F. Cocke to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1828 May 21 (Box 3)
- Mrs. John Faulcon to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1828 July 7 (Box 3)
- General John H. Cocke to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1828 July 19 (Box 3)
- Mrs. John Faulcon to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1828 July 29 (Box 3)
- Mrs. M. S. Bradley to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1828 July (Box 3)
- Mrs. Augusta E. Randolph to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1828 August 1 (Box 3)
- Mrs. Sukey [J.] Harrison to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1828 August 1 (Box 3)
- L. R. Smith to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1828 August 10 (Box 3)
- Mrs. John Faulcon to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1828 August 19 (Box 3)
- Mrs. James Maxwell to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1828 August 25 (Box 3)
- Mr. H. M. Stribling to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1828 August 25 (Box 3)
- Miss Susan I. Harrison to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1828 September 5 (Box 3)
- Birthday Resolution of Sally Faulcon Cocke 1828 September 8 (Box 3)
- Miss Mary E. Terrell to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1828 October 5 (Box 3)
- Mrs. John Faulcon to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1828 October 16 (Box 3)
- Miss Susan I. Harrison to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1828 November 1 (Box 3)
- General John H. Cocke to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1828 November 6 (Box 3)
- Mrs. S. A. Pool to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1828 November 18 (Box 3)
- Mrs. S. A. Pool to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1828 December 5 (Box 3)
- Mrs. M. S. Bradley to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1828 December 14 (Box 3)
- Mrs. S. A. Pool to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1828 December 21 (Box 3)
- Mrs. M. S. Bradley to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1828 (Box 3)
- Miss Susan I. Harrison to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1828 (Box 3)
- Miss Susan I. Harrison to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1828 (Box 3)
- Mrs. S. Hurd to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1829 January 5 (Box 3)
- Miss Susan J. Harrison to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1829 January 8 (Box 3)
- Mrs. Virginia Cary to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1829 January 11 (Box 3)
- [Mrs. S. Harrison] to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1829 February 4 (Box 3)
- Sally F. Cocke to Mamma [Mrs. Louisa Cocke] 1829 February 12 (Box 3)
- Mrs. Susan A. Pool to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1829 February 17 (Box 3)
- Mrs. Virginia Cary from [Mrs. Louisa Cocke] 1829 February 25 (Box 3)
- A. B. Cocke, L. B. Faulcon and Sally Faulcon to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1829 February 26 (Box 3)
- Mrs. S. A. Pool to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1829 March 9 (Box 3)
- General John H. Cocke to Cary C. Cocke 1829 March 11 (Box 3)
- Ann B. Cocke to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1829 March 24 (Box 3)
- Mrs. L. B. Faulcon to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1829 April 20 (Box 3)
- Mrs. Sukey J. Harrison to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1829 April 22 (Box 3)
- Samuel Hurd to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1829 April 24 (Box 3)
- Miss Mary Ferrell to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1829 April 30 (Box 3)
- M. M. Robinson to [Mrs. Louisa Cocke] 1829 May 9 (Box 3)
- Rev. Jesse Armistead to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1829 May 29 (Box 3)
- General John H. Cocke to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1829 June 17 (Box 3)
- Mrs. L. B. Faulcon to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1829 June 24 (Box 3)
- Mrs. Sally Faulcon to Sister [Mrs. Louisa Cocke] 1829 July 20 (Box 3)
- Mrs. S. A. Pool to Mrs. [Louisa] Cocke 1829 July 22 (Box 3)
- Ann B. Cocke to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1829 July 22 (Box 3)
- General John H. Cocke to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1829 July 23 (Box 3)
- Miss S. [J.] Harrison to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1829 July 24 (Box 3)
- General John H. Cocke to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1829 July 27 (Box 3)
- Susan Maxwell to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1829 July 28 (Box 3)
- Mrs. S. A. Pool to [Mrs. Louisa Cocke] 1829 August 2 (Box 3)
- H. M. Stribling to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1829 August 3 (Box 3)
- Mr. Wm. Maxwell to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1829 August 4 (Box 3)
- Mrs. M. L. Barraud to Mrs. [Louisa] John H. Cocke 1829 August 4 (Box 3)
- General John H. Cocke to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1829 August 5 (Box 3)
- Mrs. S. A. Pool to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1829 August 15 (Box 3)
- [Miss] S[ukey] J. H[arrison] to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1829 August 19 (Box 3)
- General John H. Cocke to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1829 August 28 (Box 3)
- Mrs. S. A. Pool to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1829 September 2 (Box 4)
- A[nn] B. C[ocke] to [Mrs. Louisa Cocke] 1829 September 7 (Box 4)
- Mrs. S. A. Pool to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1829 September 18 (Box 4)
- E. C. Bondoin to [Mrs. Louisa Cocke] 1829 September 23 (Box 4)
- General John H. Cocke to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1829 September 23 (Box 4)
- Miss Sukey J. Harrison to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1829 September 24 (Box 4)
- Charles C. Cocke and Jolin H. Cocke to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1829 September 8 (Box 4)
- Mrs. S. A. Pool to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1829 November 4 (Box 4)
- M. L. and D. C. Barraud to Mrs. John H. Cocke 1829 December 4 (Box 4)
- Mrs. Augusta Randolph to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1829 December 8 (Box 4)
- Mrs. Virginia Cary to Mrs. [Louisa] Cocke 1829 December 12 (Box 4)
- Mrs. L. Robertson to Mrs. [Louisa] Cocke 1829 December 16 (Box 4)
- [Miss] S[ukey] J. H[arrison] to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1829 December 21 (Box 4)
- Mrs. S. A. Pool to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1829 December 24 (Box 4)
- Mrs. Sarah Wilson to [Mrs. Louisa Cocke] 1829 December 24 (Box 4)
- Miss S[ukey] J. H[arrison] to [Mrs. Louisa Cocke] 1829 July (Box 4)
- Mrs. L. B. Faulcon to [Mrs. Louisa Cocke] [1829] February 15 (Box 4)
- Miss Ann B. Cocke to Mrs. Louisa Cocke [1829] July 26 (Box 4)
- Miss M. E. Terrell to Mrs. [Louisa] Cocke 1830 January 9 (Box 4)
- Mrs. Augusta Randolph to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1830 January 11 (Box 4)
- Mrs. S. A. Pool to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1830 January 25 (Box 4)
- Ann B. Cocke to Cary C. Cocke 1830 January 27 (Box 4)
- Miss S. J. Harrison to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1830 February 10 (Box 4)
- Mrs. [Lelia?] Robertson to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1830 March 6 (Box 4)
- Miss M. E. Terrell to [Mrs. Louisa Cocke] [1830] March 9 (Box 4)
- Mrs. Virginia Cary to Mrs. [Louisa] Cocke 1830 March 15 (Box 4)
- Miss S. J. Harrison to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1830 March 28 (Box 4)
- General John H. Cocke to Cary C. Cocke 1830 April 14 (Box 4)
- Mrs. S. A. Pool to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1830 April 20 (Box 4)
- Miss S. J. Harrison to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1830 April 26 (Box 4)
- General John H. Cocke to Cary C. Cocke 1830 May 5 (Box 4)
- Mrs. Virginia Cary to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1830 May 8 (Box 4)
- Clarinda C. Anderson to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1830 May 28 (Box 4)
- Mrs. Peyton (Jane C.) Harrison to [Mrs. Louisa Cocke] 1830 June 17 (Box 4)
- Mrs. Peyton (Jane C.) Harrison to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1830 June 26 (Box 4)
- Mary Jane Duncan to Mrs. Luisi [Louisa] Cocke 1830 July 1 (Box 4)
- Miss S. J. Harrison to [Mrs. Louisa Cocke] 1830 July 2 (Box 4)
- C. C. Anderson to Mrs. [Louisa] Cocke 1830 July 4 (Box 4)
- Miss Ann B. Cocke to Mr. Cary C. Cocke 1830 July 7 (Box 4)
- Mrs. S. A. Pool to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1830 July 16 (Box 4)
- Mary Jane Duncan to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1830 July 18 (Box 4)
- Miss S. J. Harrison to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1830 July 24 (Box 4)
- Edmund Ruffin to Cary C. Cocke 1830 (Box 4)
- ______ to Mrs. [Louisa] Cocke [1830] (Box 4)
- Cary C. Cocke to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1831 April 11 (Box 4)
- S. Hurd to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1831 June 16 (Box 4)
- Courtney Bowdoin to [Mrs. Louisa Cocke] 1831 June 16 (Box 4)
- Mrs. L. C. Page to [Mrs. Louisa Cocke] 1831 June 23 (Box 4)
- Miss S[usan] J. Harrison to [Mrs. Louisa Cocke] 1831 July 1 (Box 4)
- Mrs. Mary F. Robertson to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1831 July 6 (Box 4)
- Miss S[usan] J. Harrison to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1831 July 29 (Box 4)
- Miss Clementina to Mrs. [Louisa] Cocke 1831 July 29 (Box 4)
- Mrs. M. F. Robertson to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1831 August 1 (Box 4)
- Ann B. Cocke to [Mrs. Louisa Cocke] [1831] August 13 (Box 4)
- Mrs. Delia Hurd to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1831 August 17 (Box 4)
- Mrs. S. A. Pool to Mrs. Louisa Cocke [1831] August 19 (Box 4)
- Mrs. Helen Read to [Mrs.] Louisa [Cocke] [1831] September 17 (Box 4)
- Mrs. Ann B. Cabell to [Mrs. Louisa Cocke] 1831 September 21 (Box 4)
- Mrs. M. F. Robertson to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1831 September 24 (Box 4)
- General John H. Cocke to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1831 October 10 (Box 4)
- General John H. Cocke to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1831 October 15 (Box 4)
- Mrs. P. (Jane C.) Harrison to [Mrs. Louisa Cocke] 1831 October 15 (Box 4)
- Cary C. Cocke to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1831 October 23 (Box 4)
- Ann B. Cabell to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1831 October 31 (Box 4)
- Mrs. Delia A. Hurd to Mr. and Mrs. [Jno.] Cocke 1831 November 15 (Box 4)
- Charles C. Cocke to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1831 November 6 (Box 4)
- Mrs. M. L. Barraud to Mrs. L[ouisa] Cocke 1831 November 8 (Box 4)
- Mrs. M. J. Robertson to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1831 November 16 (Box 4)
- Mrs. M. J. Robertson to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1831 November 16 (Box 4)
- Cary C. Cocke to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1831 November 25 (Box 4)
- Mrs. Susan A. Pool to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1831 November 27 (Box 4)
- Mrs. Delia Hurd to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1831 December 3 (Box 4)
- General John H. Cocke to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1831 December 13 (Box 4)
- General John H. Cocke to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1831 December 17 (Box 4)
- S. F. Cocke to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1831 December 17 (Box 4)
- Mrs. Ann B. Cabell to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1831 December 27 (Box 4)
- Cary C. Cocke to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1832 April 4 (Box 4)
- Mrs. Delia [Hurd] to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1832 June 26 (Box 4)
- Mrs. S. A. Poole to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1832 July 16 (Box 4)
- Mrs. S. A. Poole to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1832 July 25 (Box 4)
- Miss S[usan] J. Harrison to [Mrs. Louisa Cocke] 1832 July 29 (Box 4)
- Mrs. M. L. Barraud to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1832 August 2 (Box 4)
- Mrs. Jane B. Smith to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1832 August 3 (Box 4)